<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RETURNDATA xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://Schema-URL/Schema.xsd">
  <OVERVIEW_CONTENT>By using projects hierarchy you can organize projects in a hierarchy tree , that you can collects the projects which are related to each other under a specific level or node and this level could be a child from another level, it is just an organization chart for projects. </OVERVIEW_CONTENT>
  <DATA MODULEID="001" LINKID="002" FUNCTIONALITYID="017">
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>1</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Get Project Level </ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>To get the project level details , navigate in the tree at the left hand side till you find the required level , select it and then press the button " Get Element " at the bottom of the tree .

Note : 
- In this tree you can just get the details of the level not the project.
- In the tree the level node appears in black color but project appears in red color  as you see in the picture.

</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>getPrjLevel.JPG</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>2</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Add New Project Level</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>To add a new project level, first press 'new project level' button as shown in the picture then enter the level details :
select level parent if exist, enter the level name and description , then press the add button,  you will find the level added to the tree.
</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>standardNew.gif</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>3</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Delete Project Level</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>To delete a project level, select the required level from the tree and then press the button  " Get Element " at the bottom of the tree then press the delete button , the level will be deleted from the tree.

Note: You can not delete the level if it has previous relations with projects, you should remove any projects associated with it before delete.


</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>imgdelete.gif</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>4</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Add Project To Project Level</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>To add a project to project level , select a project level from the tree then press the " Get Element " button, at the section of assigned projects select a project from the combo box and then press the add project button at the bottom of the section.</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>addPrjToLvl.JPG</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>5</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Remove Project From Project Level</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>To remove a project(s) from project level , select a project level from the tree then press the " Get Element " button, at the section of assigned projects select the project (s) from the grid and then press the remove project button at the bottom of the section.</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>rmvPrjToLvl.JPG</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
  </DATA>
</RETURNDATA>