<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RETURNDATA xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://Schema-URL/Schema.xsd">
  <OVERVIEW_CONTENT>Managing all user groups , thier user accounts and the roles associated with them</OVERVIEW_CONTENT>
  <DATA MODULEID="001" LINKID="008" FUNCTIONALITYID="015">
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>1</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Add User Group</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>Click the new user button at the bottom of the users list, type in the group name in the text box that will appear for you and click add Group</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>addUsrGrp.GIF</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>2</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Delete User Group</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>Check the check boxes in front of the user group you want to delete then click delete user group</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>delUsrGrp.GIF</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>3</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Add User To User Group</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>To assign a user to become a member of a user group, select a user group and click add user, select the check boxes in front of the users you want to add and then click the add user button at the bottom of the screen. to search for a certain user name , type your search query in the text box and click find</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>addUsrToUsrGrp.GIF</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>4</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Remove User From User Group</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>Check the checkboxes in front of the users you want to remove from the group and then click remove user</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>remvUsrFrmUsrGrp.GIF</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>5</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Add Role To User Group</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>To assign a role to a user group, select a user group and click add role button, select the check boxes in front of the roles you want to add and then click the add  button at the bottom of the screen. to search for a certain user name , type your search query in the text box and click find</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>addRoleToUsrGrp.GIF</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>6</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Remove Role From User Group</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>Check the checkboxes in front of the roles you want to remove from the group and then click remove role</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>rmvRoleFrmUsrGrp.GIF</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>7</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Security Overview</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>A security rule represents the smallest functionality that can be done by the system, like Add Employee, Terminate Employee, or running a Certain Query, a developer using the ERP Framework can define such rules and checks for each rule before executing any method.

 

Entities

To allow the ERP server to customize access rights to the very last detail; the ERP keeps a list of Major Entities Used in the system, Example for Entities:

Employee 
Project 
Team 
Entities are defined in the system database in the table SEC_Entites, the developer can related the entity to a group of Security Rules, so these rules cannot be assigned to a user explicitly they must be associated with a certain entity for example: 

If we relate the A Security Rule named “Assign Task to an Employee “ to the Entity “Employee”, the user cannot assign tasks to any employee but only those he has been given access too only.

 

User Groups

System users can be grouped together in groups to ease the assignment of access rights, a user can be a member of any number of groups and his access rights are the union of the access rights granted to the groups, he is a members.

Admin Users

A user can be marked as Admin
</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>sec1.bmp</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
  </DATA>
</RETURNDATA>