<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RETURNDATA xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://Schema-URL/Schema.xsd">
  <OVERVIEW_CONTENT>This is the company hierarchy for all departments , divisions , managers and job titles associated with every department or division.
</OVERVIEW_CONTENT>
  <DATA MODULEID="001" LINKID="006" FUNCTIONALITYID="004">
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>1</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Get Company Element Details</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>Select a company element from the tree view , then click the Get Element Details button, the details will appear in the panel to the left </ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>departHeirarchy.JPG</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>2</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Add New Company Element</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>To add a new company element press on the add new button as shown in the picture to prepare the adding operation, enter element details by selecting the element parent if exist , enter the name , select the element manager , select the element level whether it is a department or division and enter the description of the element then press the save button the tree will be added then to the tree.  </ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>Newdepar.JPG</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>3</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Edit Company Element</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>To edit an element you should first select it from the tree and then press on the 'Get Element' button you will find the element details appeared in the element form, make your changes and updates you want and then press on the save button as shown in the picture.</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>standardSave.gif</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>4</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Delete Company Element</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>To delete an element you should first select it from the tree and then press on the 'Get Element' button you will find the element details appeared in the element form, then press on the delete button as shown in the picture.

Note: if the element has relationships with other entities like it is connected with some job titles, these relationships should be removed first before deleting.
</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>imgdelete.gif</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>5</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Add Job Title To Company Element</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>For each element we need to specify the job titles that can work in this element, to add a job title to an element first select an element from the tree view and press on the ' Get Element ' button, then open the combo box of job titles, then select a job title and then press on Add selected job title button you will find then the job title added to the table of job titles.
</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>AddJobToElm.JPG</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>6</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Remove Job Title  From Compnay Element</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>To remove a job title from an element first select the element from the tree view and press on the ' Get Element ' button, then select the job title you want to remove from the job titles table by checking on the check box of it then press on the remove selected job title, you will find the job title has been removed from the table.</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>RmvJobFrmElm.JPG</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
  </DATA>
</RETURNDATA>