<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RETURNDATA xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://Schema-URL/Schema.xsd">
  <OVERVIEW_CONTENT>By accountability sheet you can view your daily entries through a deterministic week , for each day you can add your working hours in the tasks , add your comments , ( edit , delete and add new tasks  ) for your self or your managed employees also you can print your task sheet reports.</OVERVIEW_CONTENT>
  <DATA MODULEID="001" LINKID="001" FUNCTIONALITYID="008">
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>1</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Add Task</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>The employee can add task to himself by selecting a specific responsibility 
And then press the add task button, the task window will open 
Fill the task details and then press save you will find the task added under the selected responsibility

note:  you can not add task under project as this should be done by the project manager.
</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>Addbutton.gif</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>2</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Edit Task</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>The employee can select task and then press the edit task button, the task window will open make your updates and then press save
Note : you can not update a project task or a completed task
</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>edit.gif</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>3</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Close Task</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>You can select an opened task and then press the close task button at the top of the page, a window will be opened to add a comment , the task then closed and it’s color will be changed.

Note: you can not close a task has been assigned to you from your team leader or your manager
</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>imgcomplete.gif</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>4</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Delete Task</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>The employee can delete a task by selecting task and then press the delete task button, the task will be deleted.

Note:  the task should not have previous entries to be deleted.
</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>imgdelete.gif</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>5</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Change Task Responisbility</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>You can change the task responsibility by selecting a task and then press the change responsibility button , a window will be opened 
Select the new responsibility and press save.
</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>Response.jpg</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>6</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>View Assignment Accountability</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>You can view all entries for an assignment by selecting a task and then press the view assignment accountability button, a window will be opened containing all the entries for this assignment .
</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>imgAssAcc.gif</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>7</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>View Weekly Accountability Sheet</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>You can view the weekly accountability sheet by pressing the (weekly accountability sheet) button, a report will be opened containing all the entries for the selected week.</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>imgacc.gif</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>8</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Add Task Daily Entry </ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>You can enter your daily worked hours by selecting a specific cell for a specific task and day then enter the number of hours you spent in this task.
you can also add your comments for the day.

Note:  the maximum number of hours is 24.
           just numbers are allowed to be entered.

</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>taskSheet.GIF</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>9</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Calendar</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>You can search for your previous entries in a specific day by clicking on the calendar button a calendar box will open navigate trough it till you find your day  , select it and then you will get the task sheet for the selected week.
</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>calender.GIF</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>10</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>View days off</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>You can control viewing days off in the task sheet by hit the view days off checkbox , if it is checked then the days off will appears in the task sheet if it is not checked then it will be invisible.</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>dayOff.GIF</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>11</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>View Mode</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>You can control viewing the task sheet by slecteing the mode you want to view the task sheet with , there are exist 3 modes

1- General : wich will view all employee's tasks related to his responsibilities and projects  ( responsibilities and projects will appears ).

2- Projects: which will view all employee's tasks related to his projects regardless the responsibilities it belongs to ( responsibilities will not appear in the task sheet ) .

3- Tasks Only: which will view all employees’ tasks regardless its projects or responsibilities it belongs to ( responsibilities and projects will not appears ) .
</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>viewMode.GIF</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>12</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Search For Employee</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>You can search for a specific employee by clicking on search button at the top of the page a window will open search for your employee then select him by pressing the view button in the grid you will then return directly to the task sheet page and you will find the employee task sheet appears.
</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>empSearch.bmp</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>13</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Navigate Through Employees</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>You can navigate through the employees names in the combo box by using next arrow button and the previous arrow button.</ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>empNaviagte.bmp</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
    <ITEM_DATA>
      <ITEMID>14</ITEMID>
      <ITEMPARENT>0</ITEMPARENT>
      <ITEM_NAME>Colors Bar</ITEM_NAME>
      <ITEM_DESCRIPTION>Hour based task: If you choose to plane your task as hour planned task (in add task window) the task will be shown in gray.

Count based task: If you choose to plane your task as number planned task (in add task window) the task will be shown in this yellow.

Complete task: If you press close task as mentioned before you will find the task turned to be light coral color in the accountability table

N/C Task: If you choose to plane your task as not accounted planned task (in add task window) the task will be shown in this way </ITEM_DESCRIPTION>
      <IMAGENAME>taskColors.GIF</IMAGENAME>
    </ITEM_DATA>
  </DATA>
</RETURNDATA>